<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="mensagens">
        <item>Do not worry # Jesus Christ # Do not be anxious, for the morrow; because tomorrow will worry about itself."\n"Sufficient for the day is its own trouble.</item>
        <item>Truth and Love # Mahatma Gandhi # When I despair, I remember that throughout history the truth and love has always won. There have been tyrants and murderers and for a time seemed invincible but in the end always fell. Think about it! Always.</item>
        <item>The largest company # Augusto Cury # I may have defects, eager to live and get angry sometimes, but do not forget that my life is the world largest company. And I can prevent it from going bankrupt. Being happy is to recognize that life is worth living, despite all the challenges, misunderstandings and periods of crisis. Being happy is to stop being a victim of the problems and the authoring of history itself. It is cross deserts outside himself, but being able to find an oasis in the secret of his soul. I thank God every morning for the miracle of life. To be happy is not being afraid of your own feelings. You know talk about himself. It is having the courage to hear "not". You have security to receive criticism, even unfair.</item>
        <item>Make Today, Not Tomorrow # Emmanuel/Chico Xavier # The sluggard says, "Tomorrow I will" "\n" exclaims the weak:.. "Tomorrow I will have forces" "\n" asserts the offender: "Tomorrow regenero me". " \n "It is imperative to recognize, however, that the creature, deferring personal effort, not reached yet, the real sense of time. Who does not take advantage of the blessing to day lives far from the century glory. The soul not daring to move a hundred steps will not walk twenty thousand. The farmer who loses the time of sowing can not predict the consequences of procrastination of the service to which it devotes because, between one and another, there may be impediments and undefinable term struggles. A lot of people waiting for death to get a good life. But the law is clear regarding the allocation of each of us. Always achieve the results we set ourselves. If all birds have wings, not all fit on the same task or glide at the same level. Swallow flies toward the spring weather but the crow, generally devotes at any time, the floor of debris. What man now seeks surprise tomorrow, ahead of the eyes and around the heart. Take care, therefore, to make, without delay, as should be done for the benefit of your own happiness, because tomorrow will be very enjoyable and beneficial only to one who works in the well, which grows on the top and perfect ideal in blessed hours Today.</item>
        <item>Blessed # Author Unknown # Happy is he who can already receive as naturally gain and loss, right and wrong, triumph and fall, life and death.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>